Thank you all for coming to my talk this evening.
It's nice to see so many people in the audience.
For those of you who don't know very much about PS Camping, let me
start by giving you some background information about the company.
The company started twenty-five years ago.
It actually opened as a retail chain selling camping equipment,
and then twenty years ago, it bought a small number of campsites in the
UK,
and began offering camping holidays.
The company grew rapidly and has been providing holidays in continental Europe for the
last fifteen years.
If you book a camping holiday with us, you'll have a choice of over
three hundred sites.
In Italy we now have some 64 sites that we either own,
or have exclusive use of.
France is where we have the majority of sites,
and we currently have a project to expand into Switzerland.
We also have a number of sites in Northern Spain, particularly in the mountainous
region of Picos de Europa.
We've upgraded all these Spanish sites,
and improved them considerably from their original three-star rating.
We believe our holidays offer superb facilities for the whole family.
Parents who want their children to be fully occupied for all
or part of the day can take advantage of our children's activities.
These are organised by our well-qualified and enthusiastic staff:
Each day kicks off with a sports match, perhaps football,
or volleyball, followed by an hour of drama for everyone.
This may include singing or dancing, mime or other activities.
In the afternoon, there's a different art activity for each day of the week including a poster competition
or model making.
What's more, our sites are truly child-friendly,
and, with this in mind, we operate a no-noise rule in the evenings.
Children's evening activities usually finish at 9.30,
or occasionally 10,
and from 10.30 holiday-makers are expected to be quiet in the areas where there
are tents.
We want nothing to go wrong on a PS Camping holiday,
but if it does, we also want all customers to be insured.
If you haven't organised an annual insurance policy of your own you'll need to
take out the low-cost cover we offer and we require that you arrange this
when you make your holiday reservation.
There are many advantages to choosing PS Camping,
and to recommending it to others.
As a regular customer, you'll be kept informed of special offers,
and your friends can benefit from ten per cent off their holiday,
or book a luxury tent for the price of a standard one.
In return, we'll send you a thank-you present,
which you can choose from a list of high-quality items.
When it comes to our tents, these are equipped to the highest standard.
We really do think of every essential detail, from an oven
and cooking rings fuelled by bottled gas, to mirrors in the bedroom areas.
If you don't want to cook indoors, you can borrow a barbecue if you
ask in advance for one to be made available,
and there's even a picnic blanket to sit on outside your tent.
Inside, a box of games and toys can be found,
and children's tents can be hired if required.
All tents have a fridge,
and if you want to spend the day on the beach, for example, ask
for a specially designed PS Camping cool box,
which will keep your food and drinks chilled.
There are excellent washing facilities at all our sites, with washing machines
and clothes lines in the central areas, along with mops
and buckets in case your tent needs cleaning during your stay.
All sites have a cafe and/or a shop for those who'd rather 'eat in'
than dine at a local restaurant.